[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Well, I'm going to ask Mr. Lauer which is more cutthroat, the race for the White House or the morning TV awards?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "ask", "Mr.", "Lauer", "which", "is", "more", "cutthroat", ",", "the", "race", "for", "the", "White", "House", "or", "the", "morning", "TV", "awards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "This show is not where I want it to be right now.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "show", "is", "not", "where", "I", "want", "it", "to", "be", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Lauer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Am I going to get a word in here?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "going", "to", "get", "a", "word", "in", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "What are you -- what do you think -- I mean, it's like it's -- what are you literally --are you thinking about what I'm going to do with the kids this weekend or are you -- are already fashioned the show in your head?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "--", "what", "do", "you", "think", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "like", "it", "'s", "--", "what", "are", "you", "literally", "--", "are", "you", "thinking", "about", "what", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "do", "with", "the", "kids", "this", "weekend", "or", "are", "you", "--", "are", "already", "fashioned", "the", "show", "in", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "I'm thinking about what's changed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "thinking", "about", "what", "'s", "changed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["weekend"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You're biting, you want -- so what would break the rules if Matt Lauer engaged?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "biting", ",", "you", "want", "--", "so", "what", "would", "break", "the", "rules", "if", "Matt", "Lauer", "engaged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "It doesn't and I do.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "and", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Lauer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Word association?", "question_tokens": ["Word", "association", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Word association.", "answer_tokens": ["Word", "association", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Katie Couric?", "question_tokens": ["Katie", "Couric", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Extraordinarily talented.", "answer_tokens": ["Extraordinarily", "talented", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katie Couric"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "How about that thug, Al Roker?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "that", "thug", ",", "Al", "Roker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "AUER: Exactly the same guy off the air as he is on the air.", "answer_tokens": ["AUER", ":", "Exactly", "the", "same", "guy", "off", "the", "air", "as", "he", "is", "on", "the", "air", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Too many kids on Ritalin, Matt?", "question_tokens": ["Too", "many", "kids", "on", "Ritalin", ",", "Matt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I'm just saying.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "But aren't there examples where it works?", "question_tokens": ["But", "are", "n't", "there", "examples", "where", "it", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Matt.", "answer_tokens": ["Matt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "To come back at 25, how do you view it?", "question_tokens": ["To", "come", "back", "at", "25", ",", "how", "do", "you", "view", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "It's crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What's going through your mind at that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "at", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Let him keep going.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "him", "keep", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "He's doing this just for the haircut?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "doing", "this", "just", "for", "the", "haircut", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Young ingenue.", "answer_tokens": ["Young", "ingenue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katie Couric", "Matt Lauer"]}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "``", "NN", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Can you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "This is \"Today\" with Katie Couric and Matt Lauer.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "``", "Today", "''", "with", "Katie", "Couric", "and", "Matt", "Lauer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "If you're going to pick one, the one that you go, you know what, how did I not ask that?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "pick", "one", ",", "the", "one", "that", "you", "go", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "how", "did", "I", "not", "ask", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", ",", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "You know, normally it's there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "normally", "it", "'s", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Does it bother you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "bother", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "It did in the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "did", "in", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What do you want to do with the show different?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "to", "do", "with", "the", "show", "different", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I want to make it better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "make", "it", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "How does that change when you come to work in the morning?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "change", "when", "you", "come", "to", "work", "in", "the", "morning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Lights a little bit of fire under our butts, there's no question about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Lights", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "fire", "under", "our", "butts", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Do you think both these guys get it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "both", "these", "guys", "get", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How are you, doc?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "doc", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Thank you very much, Donny.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "very", "much", ",", "Donny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What did we do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "we", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I'll walk you through it, but if I walk you through it, I'm going to extend it to everybody who is watching right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "walk", "you", "through", "it", ",", "but", "if", "I", "walk", "you", "through", "it", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "extend", "it", "to", "everybody", "who", "is", "watching", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Now your height is -- you're about five-ten?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "your", "height", "is", "--", "you", "'re", "about", "five-ten", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Do you know how much the average sexual encounter burns off in calories?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "the", "average", "sexual", "encounter", "burns", "off", "in", "calories", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Hundred.", "answer_tokens": ["Hundred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Does -- what does that actually mean to reinvent the sexual relationship?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "--", "what", "does", "that", "actually", "mean", "to", "reinvent", "the", "sexual", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "It involves all that.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "involves", "all", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "What is one thing a guy at home should take away from this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "one", "thing", "a", "guy", "at", "home", "should", "take", "away", "from", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Most women have the equivalent of a G-spot.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "women", "have", "the", "equivalent", "of", "a", "G-spot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "They do?", "question_tokens": ["They", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "You have to excite that part of the female anatomy.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "excite", "that", "part", "of", "the", "female", "anatomy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Doc, that's a human livers?", "question_tokens": ["Doc", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "human", "livers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "All human livers.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "human", "livers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 726, "question": "This fatty liver -- having trouble with those gloves?", "question_tokens": ["This", "fatty", "liver", "--", "having", "trouble", "with", "those", "gloves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 727, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "What kind of doctor would you have been?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "doctor", "would", "you", "have", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "I want to use one hand.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "use", "one", "hand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "What does that cause?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "cause", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "Bad liver.", "answer_tokens": ["Bad", "liver", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 752, "question": "Isn't this stunning?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "this", "stunning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "But when you have a liver that's turned to fat and making bad cholesterol, and that same belly fat is causing high blood pressure and problems with diabetes, you get a heart like this.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "have", "a", "liver", "that", "'s", "turned", "to", "fat", "and", "making", "bad", "cholesterol", ",", "and", "that", "same", "belly", "fat", "is", "causing", "high", "blood", "pressure", "and", "problems", "with", "diabetes", ",", "you", "get", "a", "heart", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Very quickly, if I want to get from that to the better heart, the five simple things to do?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "if", "I", "want", "to", "get", "from", "that", "to", "the", "better", "heart", ",", "the", "five", "simple", "things", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Figure out the blood pressure issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Figure", "out", "the", "blood", "pressure", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "Is there another button to push?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "another", "button", "to", "push", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "I'll give you the big button.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "give", "you", "the", "big", "button", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120530pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Want the heart?", "question_tokens": ["Want", "the", "heart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "I'm going to bring that home with me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "bring", "that", "home", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]